{
    "id": "cefb11a567ae4e40b64a823d9bf7f059",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Mia can sing beautifully, and ……………………..",
            "description": "\r\nSo can be used in the structure so + auxiliary verb + subject. This structure is used to add to the sentence before.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "so her sister can",
                "her sister can also",
                "so can her sister"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never eaten …………………………. food in my life.",
            "description": "We use so much before an uncountable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "so much",
                "so many",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has ………………………. children to take care of.",
            "description": "We use so many before plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "so many",
                "so much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They held the ceremony on a Sunday …………………………… everybody would be able to attend.",
            "description": "The structures so that and in order that are used to talk about purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "in order that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Send the parcel express so that they ……………………….. it before Friday.",
            "description": "After so that and in order that, we can use a present or future tense to refer to future.",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "will get",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There are ………………………. children at the front door.",
            "description": "We use some in affirmative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "any",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You haven’t got ………………………… manners.",
            "description": "We use any in questions and negative sentences.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We met ………………………….. interesting people on holiday.",
            "description": "We use some in affirmative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "any",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… people want to go to the movies.",
            "description": "We use some before a noun without a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Some",
                "Some of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… us want to go to the movies.",
            "description": "Before a pronoun we use some of.",
            "answers": [
                "Some",
                "Some of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is little point in doing ………………………… more work now.",
            "description": "Any can be used in affirmative clauses after words like little and hardly.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There is somebody outside who ……………………………. to talk to you.",
            "description": "Somebody usually refers to only one person.",
            "answers": [
                "want",
                "wants",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}